A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Subject Files, Series 3 FA137
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Subject Files, Series 3
1902-1965
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA137
28.2 Cubic Feet 77 document boxes.
77 document boxes.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 210-3
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Other Finding Aids
FA811 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Henry James Subject Files, Series 1.
FA808 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Correspondence, Series 2.
FA809 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Annual Reports, Series 4.
FA810 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Budget Histories, Series 7.
Arrangement
As received.
Scope and Contents
Subject files of interest to Rockefeller University.
Vivisection; Cell and biomolecular sciences; Prevention and health; Biology -- Research; Biochemistry; Hospitals; Medical technology; Medical research; Life sciences; Operations management; Medicine, Preventive
- Subject files, 1902-1965; 3
  Scope and Contents note
  Administrative correspondence, papers and reports.
  Arrangement note
  Arranged in alphabetical order by subject (chronological within folders).
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Limited access. Contains some personnel and salary information.
  - Materials from the Business Manager's office, 1902-1965; 1.8 Cubic Feet; 34 boxes
    Including early items before a Business Manager was appointed. Consists of materials for meetings of the Board of Scientific Directors and its Executive Committee; some blueprints; some personnel files and retirement material; studies of some problem situations.
    - Accidents (Box 1)
    - Acetone, 1918-1949 (Box 1)
    - Aetna Insurance Company, 1925-1939 (Box 1)
      Primarily elevator and grounds inspections.
      See also Carter & Jones; Fidelity & Casualty.
    - Alcohol, 1913-1949 (Box 1)
      Includes 1918 letter from B.T. Terry about still.
    - Ambulance-Auditors (Box 1)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1928-1949 (Box 1)
    - American Cancer Society, 1936-1946 1952-1954 (Box 1)
    - American District Telegraph (fire alarms), 1913-1948 (Box 1)
    - American Hospital Association, 1920-1950 (Box 1)
    - American Medical Association, 1914-1950 (Box 1)
    - American Public Health Association, 1936-1947 (Box 2)
      - Certificate of membership, 1919
      - Certificate of Merit, 1937
    - American Red Cross, 1915-1949 (Box 2)
    - Animals, 1922-1962 (Box 2)
      Includes material on purchase, breeding and animal quarters.
    - Annuities, 1923-1939 1940-1958 (Box 2)
      Includes some meetings and resolutions; lists of retiring employees; plans.
      See also Retirement plans.
    - Applications for employment (miscellaneous), 1932-1956 (Box 2)
    - Autopsies, 1922-1947 (Box 2)
    - Ba-Bz, 1907-1925 1926-1928 (Box 3)
      Includes early correspondence on equipment; 1915 glassware ordered from J.E. Bieber, Leipzig and held up at Liverpool.
    - Babkin, Boris P., 1918-1924 (Box 3)
      Includes letter from Francis Benedict.
    - Berg-Brown (Box 3)
      Includes Roland Berg, Joseph Blake, Frederick Birchard, A.F. Blakeslee, Emil Bohnel, George Blumer, Charles C. Brown.
    - Block Community Organization, 1932 (Box 3)
    - Blood Donors, 1927-1948 (Box 3)
    - Bryn Mawr College, 1933-1938 (Box 3)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1906-1929 1930-1960 (Box 3)
      Includes running list of additions and improvements to 1933 kept By E.B. Smith.
      List of plantings; maintenance items.
    - Burglary (Wilhelm Phillips), 1916-1917 (Box 3)
    - Ca-Cz, 1906-1957 (Box 4)
      Includes March 1926 translation of letter accompanying Commemorative medal from University of Comenius.
    - Cafeteria, 1919-1961 (Box 4)
      Includes 1932 report to Mr. Fosdick (also early drafts) also material originally filed under Lunchroom.
    - Campbell, Editha, 1912-1958 (Box 4)
      Materials on personnel situation in Publications Division.
      See also 417 Flexner.
    - Cancer, 1913-1952 (Box 4)
      See also American Cancer Society.
    - Carnegie (Box 4)
      - Foundation, 1911-1920
      - Institution, 1904-1926
    - Carpenter, Samuel C., 1933-1941 (Box 4)
    - Carter & Jones, 1931-1951 (Box 4)
      See also Aetna Insurance.
    - Cartier, Ferdinand (Box 4)
      Includes photographs of his pen and ink drawings of Institute.
    - Children's Gardens, 1912-1964 (Box 5)
      Includes correspondence, photographs, newspaper items, reports.
      See also Playground.
    - Chemical Corn Exchange Bank, 1915-1958 (Box 6)
    - Clark; Clarke; Coley; Commission for Relief in Belgium; Commonwealth Fund (Box 6)
      Correspondence under Relief for Belgium deals with visiting scientists: Max Adant, Lucien Brouha. Commonwealth Fund: Eric Stiller, James Simpson.
    - Cohen, Edith A., 1924 1950 (Box 6)
      Bequest: made 1924, received 1950.
    - Columbia University, 1908-1935 (Box 6)
    - Consolidated Edison, 1917-1957 (Box 6)
      Includes blueprint of plot plan.
    - Construction, 1954-1957 (Box 6)
      Includes correspondence regarding survey of Institute holdings.
    - Coolidge Shepley Bullfinch & Abbott, 1917-1918 (Box 6)
      Construction at Princeton and Library and Assembly Room.
    - Council of National Defense (General Medical Board), 1917-1918 (Box 6)
    - Court orders (accident on F.D.R. Drive-fuel truck delivery to RIMR), 1950-1956 (Box 6)
      See also Subpoenas.
    - Cultures, 1936 (Box 6)
      Transfer to RIMR parts of U. of Chicago Jordan Colection.
    - Customs, 1907-1949 (Box 6)
      Procedures for free entry of certain items.
    - Da-Dz, 1914-1947 (Box 6)
    - Depreciation, 1916-1960 (Box 7)
    - Davis, Burt (Box 7)
      Includes correspondence and disposition dealing with injured and discharged employee.
    - Diabetes, 1915-1917 (Box 7)
    - Distemper, 1923-1928 (Box 7)
    - Dining and Residence Hall, 1952-1962 (Box 7)
      Includes some material on apartments and sub-leases.
      See also Fricke, Sophie (Fellows and Housing).
    - Dinners, 2 folders (Box 7)
      Testimonials.
      Includes Board, Cole, Flexner, Van Slyke.
      See also Faculty and student receptions.
      Arranged in alphabetical order.
    - Draft, 1917-1918 1940-1950 (Box 7)
      - Correspondence, 1940-1951
        Early correspondence and official Institute announcements; lists and summaries. Correspondence dealing with exemptions and reclassifications.
        See also Personnel (Selective Service).
    - Duffy Malt whiskey 1916 (Publicity on medical value of whiskey) (Box 7)
    - Ea-El, 1913-1948 (Box 8)
    - East River Drive, 1937-1939 1955 (Box 8)
      Includes agreements and indenture with City of NY in tunnel construction.
      See also 415.
    - Ehrlich, Paul, 1907-1910 (Box 8)
      Correspondence with Simon Flexner dealing with experimental work on tumors and chemo-therapy. Copy of Ehrlich portrait sent to S. Flexner.
    - Eimer & Amend, 1915-1934 (Box 8)
      Correspondence dealing with purchase and registration of water still.
    - Eliot, Charles W., 1907-1924 (Box 8)
      Steamship reservations; regrets concerning 10th anniversary of Institute; message from RIMR on 90th birthday.
    - Ellicott, Nancy, 1910-1938 (Box 8)
      Administrative correspondence on Hospital matters.
    - Employees, 1917-1938 1939-1948 (Box 8)
      Primarily material dealing with extension of services beyond retiring age; sick leaves and retirement provisions.
      See also Rest rooms (Employees).
    - Employees, 1949-1958 (Box 9)
    - Employees (Bonus), 1917-1944 (Box 9)
      Minutes of meetings considering extra compensation; expressions of appreciation.
    - Employees (confidential), 1908-1928 (Box 9)
      Special personnel matters.
    - Employees (Men's Committee), 1932-1940 (Box 9)
    - Equitable Trust Co. of NY, 1915-1929 (Box 9)
    - Evans, Helene R., 1915-1916 (Box 9)
    - Exhibitions, 1912-1955 (Box 9)
    - Fa-Fr, 1912-1951 (Box 9)
    - Faculty and student receptions, 1936-1956 (Box 9)
      see also Dinners (Testimonial).
    - Farm, 1913-1916 (Box 9)
      Mostly Clyde but some material on Princeton.
    - Farrand, Beatrix, 1916-1922 1933 (Box 9)
      Plans and correspondence regarding Princeton landscaping.
    - Fellowships, 1929-1952 (Box 10)
    - Fidelity and Casualty Co. (Box 10)
      Reports on boiler and elevator inspections; liability insurance and bonding of some employees.
      see also Aetna Insurance Co,.
    - Film vault, 1923-1931 1931-1939 (Box 10)
      Includes problem of new regulations regarding flammable film.
    - Finances, 1920-1963 (Box 10)
      Primarily material related to budgeting procedures including changes suggested by Cresap, McCormick & Paget, Oct. 19, 1953.
      see also 343 (l).
    - Finances, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
      Question of Hospital addition in depressed market.
    - Fire alarms, 1929-1952 (Box 10)
    - Fire precautions, 1912-1951 (Box 10)
    - Fish, Richardson, Herrick & Neave, 1913-1928 (Box 11)
      Correspondence relating to registration of "Luetin".
      Question of patent for Meltzer insufflation apparatus; Trademarks for publications.
      see also Patents 1911-1939.
    - Farley, Thomas; Flügge, C.; Forbes and Co.; Fowler, A. (Box 11)
    - Foreign students, 1930-1944 (Box 11)
    - Forms (Box 11)
      Outdated including some stationery samples.
    - Frauds, 1913-1931 (Box 11)
    - Frauds, 1932-1946 (Box 11)
    - Freas Thermo Electric Co., 1930-1934 (Box 11)
    - Fricke, Sophie (Fellows and Housing), 1959-1964 (Box 11)
      see also Dining and Residence Halls.
      see also Residence.
    - Furnishings, 1916-1962 (Box 12)
    - Ga-Gu, 1913-1961 (Box 12)
    - Garcia case, 1913-1920 (Box 12)
    - General Electric Co., 1919-1938 (Box 12)
    - Glass, 1926-1935 (Box 12)
      Includes correspondence on glass which will permit the passage of ultra-violet rays.
    - Glassblower, 1923-1945 (Box 12)
    - Gramicidin, 1939-1943 1949 (Box 12)
      Correspondence, petitions and additions in seeking Trademark including correspondence with Fish, Richardson & Neave. Includes 1940 exchange with Fish, H.S. Gasser and John Northrop on research limitation resulting from patents on some processes.
    - Grants (requests), 1908-1917 (Box 12)
    - Grants, 1913-1967 (Box 13)
      Summaries of some early grants and budgeting instructions and material on General Clinical Research Grants, 1962-1966.
    - Great Lakes Engineering Works, 1913-1918
      Installation and operation of ammonia compressor.
    - Gross, Anthony Estate (Bequest) (Box 13)
    - Grossman, Ernest, 1922 (Box 13)
      Employee accident.
    - Ha-Hu, 1912-1916 (Box 13)
    - Harvard University, 1921-1945 (Box 13)
    - Hill, James J., 1914-1916 (Box 13)
      Bequest.
      Correspondence regarding gift for study of hog cholera.
      Never received.
    - Hoof and Mouth Disease (Box 13)
    - Hospital, 1912-1945 1946-1960 (Box 13)
    - Hospital (site trips by Business Manager), 1923 1931 (Box 13)
      Correspondence between Mr. Coolidge, Dr. Cole and Simon Flexner on nurses' residence construction.
    - Hospital patients, 1923-1946 (Box 13)
      Letters of appreciation; letters of inquiry regarding certain patients sent from Rockefeller family or office.
    - Hospital, patients (legal), 1927-1960 (Box 14)
      Includes opinions and procedures from Counsel regarding release of Hospital records. Includes correspondence on Giles Verstraten.
    - Hospital staff, 1910 (Box 14)
    - Housing, 1922-1929 (Box 14)
      Blueprints and data collected in planning for building with apartments for senior scientific staff.
    - Human experimentation, 1948-1952 (Box 14)
      Letters from individuals offering their bodies for study.
    - I-Iv, 1915-1961 (Box 14)
      Includes inventory figures, 1919.
    - Illustration, 1906-1949; 2 folders (Box 14)
      Includes biographical material on Louis Schmidt; employment information on Mabel Hedge who died January 1930; photos of department and material showing development and growth of department.
    - Influenza, 1918-1945 (Box 14)
      Primarily material dealing with volunteers for sera testing 1935 under direction of D. Thomas Francis.
    - Insulin, 1923-1950 (Box 14)
      Includes original letter from John D. Rockefeller, Jr. giving $ 150,000 to be used in making insulin available for treatment of diabetes.
    - Inquiries Medical problems or areas of research, 1948-1954 (Box 15)
    - Instrument maker, 1920-1934 1935-1948 (Box 15)
    - Insurance, 1906-1963 (Box 15)
      Primarily liability accident plus very early fire insurance and bonding.
      Includes Group Life Insurance with Equitable.
    - International House, 1927-1960 (Box 15)
      Includes names and data of foreign born working in RIMR labs.
    - International Instrument Co., 1915-1933 (Box 15)
      also Standard Sci. Co. 1913-1914.
      Correspondence dealing with centrifuge.
    - Invitations, 1933-1953 (Box 15)
      Requests to send representatives to certain academic or scientific occasions including copies of letters of acceptance or regrets.
    - Ja-Ju, 1916-1953 (Box 15)
    - Jukes, Thomas Hughes (Box 15)
    - Jacques Loeb Associates in Marine Biology (O.N.R. grants), 1956-1965 (Box 15)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1923-1939 (Box 15)
    - Jury duty, 1925-1963 (Box 15)
    - Ka-kr, 1912-1948 (Box 16)
    - Keegan, Christopher D., 1920-1922 (Box 16)
      Removal of belongings from caretaker's house on RIMR grounds.
    - La-Lo, 1913-1955 (Box 16)
    - La Rosa, William, 1930-1943 (Box 16)
      Correspondence with Navy re tests for levels of sulfonamides.
    - Liquor Commission, 1933 (Box 16)
    - Lablang, Joseph Estate Bequest, 1931-1945 (Box 16)
    - Laundry, 1921-1952 (Box 16)
    - Lavoisier apartments, 1929-1947 (Box 16)
      Arrangements for Director's apartment.
    - Lavoisier painting, 1928-1940 (Box 16)
    - Lavoisier painting, 1941-1950 1951-1962 (Box 17)
      Reproductions, 8x10 colored transparency; slide; appraisal; repair to frame; requests for loan or permission to reproduce.
    - League of Nations, 1922-1946 (Box 17)
      Includes report of Dr. Agustus Wadsworth on standardization of sera conference.
    - Lee, Ivy, 1914-1954 (Box 17)
      Public relations material primarily 1914-1926.
    - Legal Aid Society, 1913-1918 (Box 17)
    - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association, 1956-1961 (Box 17)
    - Lenox Hill Playground (Box 17)
      see Playground.
    - Levene, P.A.T., 1940-1944 1945-1959 (Box 17)
      Requests for chemicals.
    - Levene, P.A.T., 1950-1963 (Box 18)
    - Library correspondence, 1909-1949 (Box 18)
    - Lindbergh, Charles A. (Box 18)
      Includes magazine and newspaper articles and reprint of report on perfusion pump.
      Includes 1928 photographs of serum delivery.
    - Luetin, 1913-1940 (Box 18)
      Correspondence regarding manufacture and maintenance of Trademark.
      See also Fish, Richardson, Herrick & Neave.
    - Lunchroom (Box 18)
      See Cafeteria.
    - Ma-Mu, 1913-1956 (Box 18)
    - Maintenance (Box 18)
      See Buildings and Grounds.
    - Mann, H.: Marsh; Maxwell; McCann Coal; McNearney (Box 18)
      Includes information about a grant to H. Mann for construction of a monocardiogram machine.
    - McFaul, Irene, 1920-1948 (Box 18)
    - Member of Alexis Carrel laboratory team (started as hospital head nurse) (Box 18)
    - Marine Biological Laboratory, 1916-1930 1931-1952 1953-1960 (Box 19)
    - Media and Glassware preparation, 1920-1949 (Box 19)
      Includes some correspondence regarding personnel; remodeling; new equipment and new charging methods.
    - Media and Glassware preparation (construction), 1927-1932 (Box 19)
    - Media and Glassware Preparation (blueprints) (Box 19)
    - Media and Glassware preparation. Charges (Box 19)
      - Institute, 1931-1954
      - I.H.D., 1934-1953
    - Meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 20)
      Enzyme Club.
      Sigma Xi.
    - Memorial Hospital, 1934-1939; 2 folders (Box 20)
      Includes land transfer, prospectus, plans, opening program, news clippings.
    - Meningitis, 1910-1934 (Box 20)
      Includes early distribution of serum and instruction for use.
      Also some information on use of serum for use abroad and some news clippings on death of some children.
    - Merck; Metal inventory; Metz, F.; Microcinematography; Moore, D.H. (Box 20)
      Includes material on Heinz Rosenberger and reprint.
    - Meyerhof, Otto (Box 20)
      Includes early bibliography; 1935 Who's Who information, handwritten letters; letters of recommendation from A.V. Hill (copy).
    - Molinscek, S.; Mount Sinai Hospital: Mugford V. (Box 20)
      Includes hospital and autopsy report on Molinscek and signed approvals of form of Minute.
    - Mousery, 1928-1934 (Box 20)
      Special rooms for Carrel cancer study with mice; tabulating machine.
      Includes material on refrigeration for greenhouses.
    - Motion picture, 1912-1928 (Box 20)
    - Motion picture, 1929-1939 (Box 21)
    - N-NZ, 1912-1959 (Box 21)
    - Naples Zoological Station, 1924-1939 (Box 21)
      Memorial table for Jacques Loeb.
    - National... (Box 21)
      Comprises: National Academy of Sciences; National Defense.
      National Recovery Act which includes letter anent painters' union.
      National Research Council which includes correspondence about a patent sought by Irving Muscat; National Science Foundation.
    - Neighborhood Development, 1937-1958 (Box 21)
      Includes material dealing with cooperative meetings: Memorial Hospital, Cornell Medical Center, RIMR, N.Y. Life Insurance Co. to improve neighborhood for the cooperating institutions.
    - Neubuck, Robert, 1926-1927 (Box 21)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, 1906-1951 (Box 21)
    - New York Botanical Gardens, 1913-1957 (Box 21)
    - New York Center for Biomathematical Research, 1960 (Box 21)
    - New York City, 1907-1916 1917-1959; 2 folders (Box 21)
      Includes early correspondence with various departments and officials dealing with water taxes, safety regulations, water supply, police protection, street cleaning.
    - New York City Fire Department, 1907-1947 (Box 21)
    - New York City Health, Dept, 1902-1963 (Box 21)
      Includes early correspondence relating to grants, anti-meningitis serum; materials from Health Department Research Bureau: Health Research Council.
    - New York Edison Company, 1904-1936 (Box 21)
    - New York State: Agriculture, Education, Health, Labor Depts (Box 22)
      Includes 1910 correspondence between Jerome Greene and Andrew Draper (Commissioner of Education) regarding State Medical exams for Hospital physicians.
    - New York State Social Welfare, Dept, 1932-1959 (Box 22)
    - New York Society for Medical Research, 1949-1951 1952-1961; 4 folders (2 of printed materials) (Box 22)
      Prior to 1951 the Society was a sub-committee on Animal Experimentation of the New York Academy of Medicine.
    - New York Telephone Company, 1905-1958 (Box 22)
    - New York University (Box 22)
      News clipping Service on Noguchi death; Noise.
    - Norris, James U., 1908-1912 (Box 23)
      Administrative correspondence with Simon Flexner and Jerome D. Greene.
    - Notices, 1932-1957 (Box 23)
      Copies of notices posted for employee information.
    - O-Oz, 1913-1953 (Box 23)
    - Obsolescence Fund, 1916-1956 (Box 23)
    - Ogden, Henry N., 1924-1925 (Box 23)
      Grant for study of milk pasteurization process.
    - Office of Naval Research; Office of Scientific Research and Development (Box 23)
    - Pa-Pz, 1912-1953 (Box 23)
    - Paasche, Eystein Karl Mørner (Box 23)
    - Packshanian, Ardzroony. Application for staff appointment, 1926-1957 (Box 23)
    - Paintings (portraits), 1910-1946 (Box 23)
    - Pamphlet revision, 1931 (Box 23)
      (See also Cartier, Ferdinand).
    - Parking facilities, 1917-1959 (Box 23)
    - Pasteur Institute (Box 24)
      Rockefeller contribution for purchase and restoration of Pasteur birthplace and presentation to the French people.
    - Patents, 1911-1940 (Box 24)
      Copies of correspondence regarding patents.
      See also Fish, Richardson, Herrick & Neave; See also Luetin.
    - Pearce, Louise. Monograph no. 23 (Box 24)
    - Pearce, Richard M., 1905-1930 (Box 24)
      Early correspondence dealing with grants, vivisection matters 1930 Memorial meeting held at RIMR.
    - Pension plans, 1913-1938 (Box 24)
    - Pensions for widows, 1920-1961 (Box 24)
    - Permits, 1920-1945 (Box 24)
    - Personnel (assorted subjects) (Box 24)
      Chronological within subject: sick leave; vaccination; chest x-rays; 1963 labor relations; grievance procedure; Princeton vacation problems.
    - Personnel (Princeton), 1933-1948 (Box 24)
    - Personnel (Selective Service) (Box 25)
    - Personnel (Scientific staff) summarized lists (Box 25)
    - Personnel (various), 1941-1965 (Box 25)
    - Pestrecov, Konstantin, 1932-1952 (Box 25)
      Correspondence relating to suit brought against Institute.
      See also 417 for release.
    - Photographs, 1906-1960 (Box 25)
      Correspondence dealing with requests for photographs and also aerial photos of Institute property.
    - Plant pathology, 1919-1953 (Box 25)
      Includes early ideas; interest in Boyce-Thompson Institute; move to New York City.
    - Playground blueprints (Box 26)
    - Playground correspondence, 1920-1921 1922-1929 1930-1942 1950 (Box 26)
      Correspondence with Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association.
    - Playground: photographs and news items (Box 26)
    - Plesmograph (Box 26)
    - Pneumonia, 1912-1937 (Box 26)
    - Pneumosintes, 1925 January-March (Box 26)
      Course for International Group on filterable virus.
    - Poliomyelitis, 1909-1957 1909-1940; 1909-1940 (Box 27)
      Correspondence on 1910 paper before Assoc. Am. Physicians by S. Flexner; advertising misuse of RIMR by John-Perrine Assoc.; 19l6 cooperative investigation of polio with NYC Health Dept. (support of Rockefeller Foundation); 1928-1931 blood collection from recovered patients for serum production (grant to NY Academy of Medicine Committee by John D. Rockefeller, Jr.); Aug. 1931 Flexner report on Poliomyelitis (see also Report of Scientific Directors Oct. 1931); includes 1939 De Kruif pamphlet "Activities of the National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis in the Field of Virus Research".
    - Princeton University, 1915-1952 (Box 27)
    - Priorities, 1941-1946 (Box 27)
    - Publication, 1929-1958 (Box 27)
      Support of plant pathology and botany journals.
    - Publication Division (Box 27)
      See Rockefeller University Press/Publication Division.
    - Publicity, 1913-1924 1925-1948 (Box 27)
      Requests for announcements and or photographs.
      Copies of News releases.
    - Publicity, 1920-1957 (Box 27)
      Announcement of staff changes and News Releases on individuals.
      Announcement of building plans with photo, 1957.
    - Purchase and supply, 1938-1949 (Box 28)
      Includes annual reports which are in greater detail than Mgr's annual reports.
    - Questionnaires, 1940-1958 (Box 28)
      Copies of replies made for Hospital Directories, Nursing Council, etc.
    - Ra-Rz, 1913-1953 (Box 28)
    - Radium, 1907-1925 1925-1959 (Box 28)